Guide to the James Ferlo Papers, 1963-2015 AIS.1998.02
ULS Archives & Special Collections
- Pittsburgh City Council, 1963-2010; 1987-2002; I.
  - Issues File, 1963-2002; 1987-2001; 9.
    - Public Utilities Commission- Report "Investigation of Uncollectible Taxes", 1992 (Box 53, Folder 2)
    - Public Works, 1991-1993 (Box 53, Folder 3)
    - Regional Assets, 1990 (Box 53, Folder 4)
    - Safe Summer, 1997 (Box 53, Folder 5)
    - Safe Summer Contributions, 1997 (Box 53, Folder 6)
    - Safe Summer Fundraising, 1995 (Box 53, Folder 7)
    - Safe Summer- General, 1995-1998 (Box 53, Folder 8)
    - Safe Summer Individual Sign-in Sheets, 1995 (Box 53, Folder 9)
    - Safe Summer Information Packet, 1995 (Box 53, Folder 10)
    - Safe Summer Materials, 1995 (Box 53, Folder 11)
    - Safe Summer Photographs, undated (Box 53, Folder 12)
    - Safe Summer Volunteers, 1995 (Box 53, Folder 13)
    - Scheleny Estate, 1993 (Box 53, Folder 14)
    - Schenely Estate (Phipps Conservatory), 1992-1993 (Box 53, Folder 15)
    - Schenley Estate (Phipps Conservatory), 1992-1993 (Box 53b, Folder 16)
    - Schenley Estate (Pleadings), 1992-1993 (Box 53b, Folder 17-19)
    - Schenley Park Golf Course, 1992-1993 (Box 53b, Folder 20)
    - Schenley Legal, circa 1992 (Box 53b, Folder 21)
    - Schenley- Standing, circa 1993 (Box 53b, Folder 22)
    - Schenley- Third Party Beneficiary, circa 1993 (Box 53b, Folder 23)
    - Sites and Delivery, 1995 (Box 53b, Folder 24)
    - Super Playground Articles, 1990-1991 (Box 53b, Folder 25)
    - Super Playground in Highland Park, Contracts for Future Use, 1991 (Box 53b, Folder 26)
    - Super Playground, Leather's Information/Industry Information, 1991 (Box 53b, Folder 27)
    - Super Playground- Chronology Forms, 1991 (Box 53b, Folder 28)
    - Super Playground- Liability, 1991 (Box 53b, Folder 29)
    - Super Playground- Original Forms, 1991 (Box 53b, Folder 30)
    - Super Playground- Photographs, undated (Box 53b, Folder 31)
    - Super Playground- Stationary, undated (Box 53b, Folder 32)
    - Syria Mosque, 1981-1992 (Box 53b, Folder 33-37)
    - Syria Mosque, 1981-1992 (Box 54, Folder 1)
    - Syria Mosque, 1983-1991 (Box 54, Folder 2)
    - Syria Mosque Agreement, 1992 (Box 54, Folder 3)
    - Syria Mosque- City Planning, 1991-1992 (Box 54, Folder 4)
    - Syria Mosque- Final Oakland Civic Historic District, circa 1992 (Box 54, Folder 5)
    - Syria Mosque- Letters- Opposed, 1992 (Box 54, Folder 6)
    - Syria Mosque- Oakland Historic District Public Hearing Lists, 1992 (Box 54, Folder 7)
    - Tow Truck Legislation, 1992-1995 (Box 54, Folder 8)
    - Urban Redevelopment and Economics, circa 2000 (Box 54, Folder 9-10)
    - Worker's Compensation, 1995-1996 (Box 54, Folder 11)
    - Youth Commission- Database File, 1993 (Box 55, Folder 1)
    - Youth Commission-Miscellaneous Research and Implementation Materials, 1990-1993 (Box 55, Folder 2)
    - Youth Commission- Nominees/ Membership, 1992-1993 (Box 55, Folder 3)
    - Youth Commission- Progress Report, 1992 (Box 55, Folder 4)
    - Youth Commission- Public Hearing, 1992-1993 (Box 55, Folder 5)
    - Youth Commission- Second Options Center, 1993 (Box 55, Folder 6)
    - Youth Commission- Updates, 1992 (Box 55, Folder 7)
    - Youth Commission- Work Papers/ Research /Other Cities, 1991-1992 (Box 55, Folder 8)
    - Zoo Privitization, 1992-1993 (Box 55, Folder 9-11)
  - Neighborhood Files, 1988-2002; 10.
    The Neighborhood Files subseries contains materials related to Pittsburgh area neighborhoods, especially those located in Ferlo's District 7, including Bloomfield, East Liberty, Friendship, Garfield, Highland Park, Lawrenceville, Morningside, Oakland, Perry, Polish Hill, Shadyside, Southside, Stanton Heights, and the Strip District.
    - Bloomfield Business Association, 1994-1996 (Box 55, Folder 12)
    - Bloomfield Business Directory, circa 2000 (Box 55, Folder 13)
    - Bloomfield Citizens Council- Correspondence, 1995-1996 (Box 55, Folder 14)
    - Bloomfield Citizens Council- Marathon, 1995-1996 (Box 55, Folder 15)
    - Bloomfield Crime, 1999 (Box 55, Folder 16)
    - Bloomfield Factory Assocation, 1994 (Box 55, Folder 17)
    - Bloomfield Garfield Corporation, 1997-2000 (Box 55, Folder 18)
    - Bloomfield Garfield Corporation- Young Employment, 1995-1996 (Box 55, Folder 19)
    - Bloomfield Issues, 1996 (Box 55, Folder 20)
    - Bloomfield- Local Neighborhood Commercial District, 1997-1999 (Box 55, Folder 21)
    - Bloomfield Marriott, 2000 (Box 55, Folder 22)
    - Bloomfield Parking Permit Concerns/Objections, 2000 (Box 55, Folder 23)
    - Bloomfield Policing Issues, 1995 (Box 55, Folder 24)
    - Bloomfield Recreation, 1998-2000 (Box 55, Folder 25)
    - Bloomfield Rectory, 2000 (Box 55, Folder 26)
    - Bloomfield Summer Jobs for Youth, 1994-1995 (Box 55, Folder 27)
    - Bloomfield Zoning Issues, 1993-1995 (Box 56, Folder 1)
    - Brookline Park Ballfield Construction, 2000 (Box 56, Folder 2)
    - Downtown Planning Collaborative-Final Report, 2000 (Box 56, Folder 3)
    - East Liberty, 1996-1997 (Box 56, Folder 4)
    - East Liberty Arts Council, undated (Box 56, Folder 5)
    - East Liberty Concerned Citizens Corporations, 1994 (Box 56, Folder 6)
    - East Liberty- Home Depot, 1998-1999 (Box 56, Folder 7)
    - Friendship Park, 1996 (Box 56, Folder 8)
    - Friendship Rezoning, 1992 (Box 56, Folder 9-10)
    - Garfield, 2000 (Box 56, Folder 11)
    - Garfield Demo, undated (Box 56, Folder 12)
    - Garfield Shopping Center, 1998 (Box 56, Folder 13)
    - Garfield Y, 2000 (Box 56, Folder 14)
    - Garfield Heights, 1990-1991 (Box 56, Folder 15)
    - Garfield Heights Advisory Committee, 1998 (Box 56, Folder 16)
    - Garfield Housing Initiative, 2000 (Box 56, Folder 17)
    - Garfield Issues, 1996 (Box 56, Folder 18)
    - Garfield Playground, 1998-1999 (Box 56, Folder 19)
    - Glen Hazel Citizens Association, 1996-1998 (Box 56, Folder 20)
    - Highland Park Community Club, 1996 (Box 56, Folder 21)
    - Highland Park Community Club- Centennial Celebration, 1996 (Box 56, Folder 22)
    - Highland Park- General, 1994-2001 (Box 56, Folder 23)
    - Highland Park Conservation of Statues, 1995-1997 (Box 56, Folder 24-25)
    - Highland Park House Tour, 1995 (Box 56, Folder 26)
    - Highland Park Issues, 1996 (Box 56, Folder 27)
    - Highland Park Mural, 1993-1996 (Box 56, Folder 28)
    - Highland Park Reservoir, 1995 (Box 56, Folder 29)
    - Highland Park Revitalization, 1999-2000 (Box 56, Folder 30)
    - Highland Park Swimming Pool, 1998 (Box 56, Folder 31)
    - Hillside Districts, 2002 (Box 56, Folder 32)
    - Lawrenceville, 1990-1992 (Box 56, Folder 33)
    - Lawrenceville, 1991-1993 (Box 56, Folder 34)
    - Lawrenceville- Berlin Way, 1994-1996 (Box 56, Folder 35)
    - Lawrenceville/Bloomfield Meals on Wheels, 1990-1991 (Box 56, Folder 36)
    - Lawrenceville Brew Pub, 1995-1996 (Box 56, Folder 37)
    - Lawrenceville Bus, 1998-1999 (Box 56, Folder 38)
    - Lawrenceville Business Association, 1993-1998 (Box 56, Folder 39)
    - Lawrenceville Business Association- Holiday Lighting Committee, 1989-1994 (Box 57, Folder 1)
    - Lawrenceville- Child Care, 2000 (Box 57, Folder 2)
    - Lawrenceville Citizens Council, 1991 (Box 57, Folder 3)
    - Lawrenceville- CISP site, 1997-1998 (Box 57, Folder 4)
    - Lawrenceville- Community Orientated Police, 1997-1998 (Box 57, Folder 5)
    - Lawrenceville- Comprehensive Service Program, 1999 (Box 57, Folder 6)
    - Lawrenceville- CSX Site, 1988-1989 (Box 57, Folder 7)
    - Lawrenceville Development Corporation, 1993-1997 (Box 57, Folder 8)
    - Lawrenceville- Engine House, 1994-1996 (Box 57, Folder 9)
    - Lawrenceville Historical Society, 1992-1997 (Box 57, Folder 10)
    - Lawrenceville Holiday Lighting, 1995 (Box 57, Folder 11)
    - Lawrenceville Ice House Redevelopment Project, 1999-2000 (Box 57, Folder 12)
    - Lawrenceville Industrial Society Access Road, 1995 (Box 57, Folder 13)
    - Lawrenceville Issues, 1996 (Box 57, Folder 14)
    - Lawrenceville Lectromelt Facility, 1994 (Box 57, Folder 15)
    - Lawrenceville Library, 1998 (Box 57, Folder 16)
    - Lawrenceville Mural Project Plan, circa 2000 (Box 57, Folder 17)
    - Lawrenceville Permit Parking, 1993 (Box 57, Folder 18)
    - Lawrenceville Permit Parking Arsenal Bowl, 1994 (Box 57, Folder 19)
    - Lawrenceville Permit Parking Expansion, 1994 (Box 57, Folder 20)
    - Lawrenceville- Physical and Human Conditions, 1996 (Box 57, Folder 21)
    - Lawrenceville Plans, 1988 (Box 57, Folder 22)
    - Lawrenceville Public Safety Readings, 1993 (Box 57, Folder 23)
    - Lawrenceville Redevelopment, 2000-2001 (Box 57, Folder 24)
    - Lawrenceville Rehabs, circa 1999 (Box 57, Folder 25)
    - Lawrenceville Riverfront Cleanup, 1993-1994 (Box 57, Folder 26)
    - Lawrenceville Shopping Plaza, 1991-1996 (Box 57, Folder 27)
    - Lawrenceville SNRP, 1999 (Box 57, Folder 28)
    - Lawrenceville Streetface Program, 1994 (Box 57, Folder 29)
    - Lawrenceville Task Force, 1991 (Box 57, Folder 30)
    - Lawrenceville Youth Football Club, 1993-1997 (Box 57, Folder 31)
    - Lawrenceville Youth and Public Safety Task Force, 1994 (Box 57, Folder 32)
    - Lawrenceville Zoning Issues, 1994-1997 (Box 57, Folder 33)
    - Lincoln Larimer Lemington Citizens Revitalization Corporation, circa 1990 (Box 57, Folder 34)
    - Lower Bloomfield Unity Council Newsletters, 1994 (Box 57, Folder 35)
    - Lower Bloomfield Unity Council- Correspondence, 1994-1996 (Box 57, Folder 36)
    - Manchester Citizens Council, 1990 (Box 57, Folder 37)
    - Morningside Area Community Council, 1990-1998 (Box 57, Folder 38)
    - Morningside Baseball Associations, 1991 (Box 57, Folder 39)
    - Morningside Blockwatch, 1995 (Box 57, Folder 40)
    - Morningside Computer Lab, 1999 (Box 57, Folder 41)
    - Morningside Issues, 1996-1997 (Box 57, Folder 42)
    - Morningside Meeting, 1994 (Box 57, Folder 43)
    - Morningside Playground, 1994-1996 (Box 57, Folder 44)
    - Mount Washington, 1995 (Box 58, Folder 1)
    - National Center for Neighborhood Enterprise, 1989-1990 (Box 58, Folder 2)
    - Neighborhood Group Fineview, 1989-1990 (Box 58, Folder 3)
    - Neighborhood Legal Services Association, 1990 (Box 58, Folder 4)
    - Neighborhood Needs, 2000-2001 (Box 58, Folder 5)
    - Neighborhood Needs Program-Tom Murphy, 1999 (Box 58, Folder 6)
    - Neighborhood Safety Program, 1989 (Box 58, Folder 7)
    - North Point Breeze, 1990 (Box 58, Folder 8)
    - North Shore, 2001 (Box 58, Folder 9)
    - North Shore Garage, 1997 (Box 58, Folder 10)
    - Northside Conference, 1990 (Box 58, Folder 11)
    - Northside Development Council, 1988 (Box 58, Folder 12)
    - Northside Tenants Organization- NTR Harriet Henson, 1988-1991 (Box 58, Folder 13)
    - Oakland Civic District, 2000 (Box 58, Folder 14)
    - Oakland BID, 2001 (Box 58, Folder 15)
    - Oakland Planning and Development Corporation, 1989-1993 (Box 58, Folder 16)
    - Overbrook Community Council, 1988 (Box 58, Folder 17)
    - Perry Hilltop Citizens Council, 1990 (Box 58, Folder 18)
    - Polish Hill, 1997-1998 (Box 58, Folder 19)
    - Polish Hill Civic Association, 1988-1995 (Box 58, Folder 20)
    - Polish Hill Issues, 1995 (Box 58, Folder 21)
    - Shadyside Action Coalition, 1988-1990 (Box 58, Folder 22)
    - Shadyside Rezoning, 1997 (Box 58, Folder 23)
    - Southside, 2001 (Box 58, Folder 24)
    - Southside Historic District, 1993 (Box 58, Folder 25)
    - Southside Local Development Company, 1990 (Box 58, Folder 26)
    - Southside LTV, 1998 (Box 58, Folder 27)
    - Spring Garden Neighborhood Council, 1988 (Box 58, Folder 28)
    - Stanton Heights, 1995-1997 (Box 58, Folder 29)
    - Stanton Heights Community Blockwatch, 1992 (Box 58, Folder 30)
    - Stanton Heights Development, 1998-1999 (Box 58, Folder 31)
    - Stanton Heights Lights, 1991 (Box 58, Folder 32)
    - Stanton Heights Recreation Association, 1991 (Box 58, Folder 33)
    - Stanton Heights Revitalization Project, 1989 (Box 58, Folder 34)
    - Stanton Heights Shopping Center, 1993-1994 (Box 58, Folder 35)
    - Strip District, 1992 (Box 58, Folder 36)
    - Strip District Parking, 1997 (Box 58, Folder 37)
    - Strip District Business, 1997 (Box 58, Folder 38)
    - Uptown Community Action Group, 1997 (Box 58, Folder 39)
    - West End Health Center, 1990 (Box 58, Folder 40)
    - Westside, 1990-1992 (Box 58, Folder 41)
    - Westside Community Development Corporation, 1990-1991 (Box 58, Folder 42)
  - Personnel Files, 1995-1998; 11.
    The Personnel Files subseries contains employee lists, pension lists, and payroll information for City employees. This subseries is currently restricted.
    - City Employee List, 1995 (Box 59, Folder 1)
    - Municipal Pension Retirees, 1996 (Box 59, Folder 2)
    - Personnel Payroll- City of Pittsburgh, 1996 (Box 59, Folder 3-4)
    - Personnel Payroll- City of Pittsburgh, 1998 (Box 59, Folder 5)
- Pennsylvania State Senate, 2000-2015; 2004-2013; II.
  The Pennsylvania Senate series documents James Ferlo's career as a Pennsylvania senator between 2003 and 2011. The series contains five subseries: Alphabetical Subject Files; Associations and Commissions; Legislation Issues and Correspondence; Job Recommendations and Requests; and State Finances. Materials include budgets, correspondence, legal materials, publications, reports, and other records related to Ferlo's political career as a Pennsylvania state senator and Pennsylvania politics during this period.
  - Alphabetical Subject Files, 2000-2014; 2003-2008; 1.
    The Alphabetical Subject File of the Pennsylvania Senate series contains Ferlo's alphabetical file of materials covering a variety of Pennsylvania-specific issues retained during his time as a senator 2003-2015.
    - 38th District Demographics, undated (Box 60, Folder 1)
    - 40th street bridge, 2003 (Box 60, Folder 2)
    - Accounting, 2003 (Box 60, Folder 3)
    - Afro-American Music Institute, 2004 (Box 60, Folder 4)
    - Alcohol, 2003 (Box 60, Folder 5)
    - Allegheny Conference on Community Development, 2003-2006 (Box 60, Folder 6)
    - Allegheny Energy, 2003 (Box 60, Folder 7)
    - Allegheny Riverfront, 2012 (Box 60, Folder 8)
    - American Institute of Architects, 2005 (Box 60, Folder 9)
    - American Institute of Architects, 2008 (Box 60, Folder 10)
    - Anti-Sweatshop Labor Campaign, 2005 (Box 60, Folder 11)
    - Apollo, PA Industrial Redevelopment Plan, August 2004 (Box 60, Folder 12)
    - Association of Municipal Management, 2005 (Box 60, Folder 13)
    - Autism Caucus, 2003-2008 (Box 60, Folder 14)
    - Aviary, 2008 (Box 60, Folder 15)
    - Bakery Square, ca 2006 (Box 60, Folder 16)
    - Ben Franklin Technology Partners, 2005 (Box 60, Folder 17)
    - B-File, ca 2007 (Box 60, Folder 18)
    - Biography (James Ferlo), 2010 (Box 60, Folder 19)
    - BioTech, 2004-2005 (Box 60, Folder 20)
    - Blind Person Issues, 2003-2004 (Box 60, Folder 21)
    - Bloomfield Development Corporation (BDC), 2008-2012 (Box 60, Folder 22)
    - Bloomfield I and Morrow Park, 2009 (Box 60, Folder 23)
    - Bloomfield II, 2005-2008 (Box 60, Folder 24)
    - Bloomfield Master Plan, 2005 (Box 60, Folder 25)
    - Bloomfield Stakeholders, 2013 (Box 60, Folder 26)
    - Bloomfield/Garfield, 2009-2011 (Box 60, Folder 27)
    - Blue Elephant, 2011 (Box 60, Folder 28)
    - Bombardier Transportation, 2004 (Box 60, Folder 29)
    - Boston Mainstreet, 2000-2001 (Box 60, Folder 30)
    - Boy Scouts, 2004 (Box 60, Folder 31)
    - Bradley Center, 2005 (Box 60, Folder 32)
    - Breweries, 2007 (Box 60, Folder 33)
    - Bryant Street, 2012 (Box 60, Folder 34)
    - Bryant Street: Bizz Buzz Event, 2012 (Box 60, Folder 35)
    - Buncher Company, 2003 (Box 60, Folder 36)
    - Candlelight Lounge, 2005 (Box 60, Folder 37)
    - Career and Workforce Division, 2002-2006 (Box 60, Folder 38)
    - Catalyst Connection, 2004-2007 (Box 60, Folder 39)
    - Caterers, undated (Box 60, Folder 40)
    - Catholic Charities Medical Clinic, 2003-2004 (Box 60, Folder 41)
    - Chester Engineers, 2012-2014 (Box 60, Folder 42)
    - Children's Hospital, 2003-2010 (Box 60, Folder 43)
    - City County Merger, 2008 (Box 60, Folder 44)
    - City/County Consolidation, 2008 (Box 60, Folder 45)
    - Clean Pittsburgh Commission, 2005-2006 (Box 60, Folder 46)
    - Coalition Against Violence, 2007 (Box 60, Folder 47)
    - Cochran Keith (Architect), 2002-2003 (Box 60, Folder 48)
    - Comcast, 2003 (Box 60, Folder 49)
    - Committee Assignments, 2010 (Box 60, Folder 50)
    - Commonwealth One, 2004 (Box 60, Folder 51)
    - Communities in Schools, 2005 (Box 60, Folder 52)
    - Community College of Allegheny County (CCAC) Job Training, 2004-2007 (Box 60, Folder 53)
    - Consol Energy, 2010 (Box 60, Folder 54)
    - Constitutional Convention, 2005-2007 (Box 61, Folder 1)
    - Consumer Advocacy, 2005-2006 (Box 61, Folder 2)
    - Convention Center Hotel, 2006 (Box 61, Folder 3)
    - Co-Ops, 2006 (Box 61, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence File, 2007-2012 (Box 61, Folder 5)
    - County Commissioners, 2009 (Box 61, Folder 6)
    - Creative and Performing Arts High School of Pittsburgh, undated (Box 61, Folder 7)
    - Cuba, 2009 (Box 61, Folder 8)
    - Daycare and Childcare, ca 2009 (Box 61, Folder 9)
    - Death Penalty, 2005 (Box 61, Folder 10)
    - Department of Community and Economic Development (DCED) Neighborhood Assistance (NAP), 2013 (Box 61, Folder 11)
    - Distressed School Districts, 2012 (Box 61, Folder 12)
    - District Justices, undated (Box 61, Folder 13)
    - District Office Information, 2003-2011 (Box 61, Folder 14)
    - Downtown, 2010-2011 (Box 61, Folder 15)
    - Duquesne University, 2009-10 (Box 61, Folder 16)
    - Durable Medical Supplies, 2005 (Box 61, Folder 17)
    - East End, 2010-2011 (Box 61, Folder 18)
    - East Liberty Development, Inc., 2010 (Box 61, Folder 19)
    - East Liberty, 2005-2007 (Box 61, Folder 20-21)
    - Energy Sector Job Analysis- PGH Region, 2012 (Box 61, Folder 22)
    - Environment (General), 2003 (Box 61, Folder 23)
    - Events, 2011 (Box 61, Folder 24)
    - Failing Schools, 2011 (Box 61, Folder 25)
    - Family Planning, 2004 (Box 61, Folder 26)
    - Family Retreat Center, 2005 (Box 61, Folder 27)
    - Family Support Center, 2003 (Box 61, Folder 28)
    - Family Support Centers, 2012 (Box 61, Folder 29)
    - Farmer's Market Relocation Advisory Committee, 2005-2007 (Box 61, Folder 30)
    - Ferrante Motor Cars, 2006 (Box 61, Folder 31)
    - Fiore, Mike, 2002 (Box 61, Folder 32)
    - Fiori Motors, 2014 (Box 61, Folder 33)
    - Fire Arms, 2004 (Box 61, Folder 34)
    - Fitzpatrick, Keino, 2008 (Box 61, Folder 35)
    - Forest Lands Beautification Program, 2005 (Box 61, Folder 36)
    - Freeport, 2008 (Box 61, Folder 37)
    - Freeport, Leechburg and Apollo Group (FLAG), 2006-2010 (Box 61, Folder 38)
    - Friendship Development, 2003 (Box 61, Folder 39)
    - G-20 Summit 1, 2009 (Box 61, Folder 40-41)
    - G-20 Summit 2, 2009 (Box 61, Folder 42-43)
    - G-20 Summit 3, 2009 (Box 62, Folder 1-2)
    - Gilda's Club, undated (Box 62, Folder 3)
    - Good Schools of PA, 2003 (Box 62, Folder 4)
    - Greater Hill Development League, 2006 (Box 62, Folder 5)
    - Greater Pittsburgh Community Foodbank, 2007 (Box 62, Folder 6)
    - Greater Pittsburgh Non-Profit Partnership, 2008 (Box 62, Folder 7)
    - Green Building Alliance, 2004 (Box 62, Folder 8-9)
    - Green Building Alliance, 2010 (Box 62, Folder 10)
    - Green Economics, 2006-2008 (Box 62, Folder 11-12)
    - Green Government Task Force, 2006-2008 (Box 62, Folder 13)
    - Health Insurance, undated (Box 62, Folder 14)
    - Highbuds Little League, 2004 (Box 62, Folder 15)
    - Highland Park, 2009-2010 (Box 62, Folder 16)
    - Highmark Blue Cross/Blue Shield Merger, 2007 (Box 62, Folder 17)
    - Highmark-Allegheny General Hospital Merger, 2012 (Box 62, Folder 18)
    - Hill District Community Benefits Agreement (CBA), 2008 (Box 62, Folder 19)
    - Hill District Community Supplement, 2008 (Box 62, Folder 20)
    - Hill District Development- RACP, 2005 (Box 62, Folder 21)
    - Hill District, 2008-2010 (Box 62, Folder 22)
    - Hill District: Community Benefits Agreement, 2007 (Box 62, Folder 23)
    - Hill House Association, 2005 (Box 62, Folder 24)
    - Hill House Economic Development Corporation/Keystone Innovation Zone, 2006 (Box 62, Folder 25)
    - Home Care Attendants, 2012-2013 (Box 62, Folder 26)
    - Homelessness, 2003 (Box 62, Folder 27)
    - Homeownership, 2004 (Box 62, Folder 28)
    - Homewood Children's Village, 2010-2011 (Box 62, Folder 29)
    - Hospitals (Southwestern PA), 2002 (Box 62, Folder 30)
    - Housing Alliance of PA, 2005-2009 (Box 62, Folder 31)
    - Housing Alliance of PA, 2012 (Box 62, Folder 32)
    - Housing: Pennsylvania Housing Finance Agency (PHFA), 2004-2005 (Box 62, Folder 33)
    - Human Service Development Fund, 2010 (Box 62, Folder 34)
    - Huntley and Huntley vs. Borough Council of the Borough of Oakmont, 2007 (Box 62, Folder 35)
    - I Networks, undated (Box 62, Folder 36)
    - iContact, 2011 (Box 62, Folder 37)
    - Idea Foundry, 2006 (Box 62, Folder 38)
    - Immigrant Integration, 2014 (Box 62, Folder 39)
    - Independent Living Centers, 2008 (Box 62, Folder 40)
    - Independent Regulatory Review Commission, 2003 (Box 62, Folder 41)
    - Indigent Criminal Defendant (Advisory Committee On…), 2008 (Box 62, Folder 42)
    - Innovation Works, 2007 (Box 62, Folder 43)
    - International Alliance of Theatrical Stage Employees (IATSE), 2007 (Box 62, Folder 44)
    - Italian and Italian American Heritage Commission, 2004 (Box 62, Folder 45)
    - John M. Phillips Historical Marker Nomination, 2009 (Box 62, Folder 46)
    - Juvenile Detention, 2003 (Box 62, Folder 47)
    - Karotest, 2000 (Box 62, Folder 48)
    - KB Forward Lanes, 2004 (Box 63, Folder 1)
    - Kennywood Park, 2012 (Box 63, Folder 2)
    - Kiski Valley Water Authority, 2002-2009 (Box 63, Folder 3)
    - Koryak, 2006 (Box 63, Folder 4)
    - Kramer, Joe, 2007 (Box 63, Folder 5)
    - Lamar-Millvale, 2006 (Box 63, Folder 6)
    - Landmark Community Capital Corp., 2008 (Box 63, Folder 7)
    - Larimer Consensus Group (LCG), 2010 (Box 63, Folder 8)
    - Larimer Consensus Group, 2010-2011 (Box 63, Folder 9)
    - Larimer Energy Center, 2009-2010 (Box 63, Folder 10-11)
    - Larimer Green Team, 2007 (Box 63, Folder 12)
    - Larimer II, 2010 (Box 63, Folder 13)
    - Larimer, 2007-2011 (Box 63, Folder 14-15)
    - Larimer, 2008 (Box 63, Folder 16)
    - Lawrenceville Business Guild (LBG) Inc., 2006 (Box 63, Folder 17)
    - Lawrenceville Corporation, 2003 (Box 63, Folder 18)
    - Lawrenceville, 2002 (Box 63, Folder 19)
    - Lawrenceville, 2008 (Box 63, Folder 20-21)
    - Lawrenceville-Heppenstahl Technology Center, 2012 (Box 63, Folder 22)
    - Leechburg, 2008 (Box 63, Folder 23)
    - Legislative District Information, 2012 (Box 63, Folder 24)
    - Liberty Tree Journal, 2008 (Box 63, Folder 25)
    - Lincoln-Lemington, 2010-2011 (Box 63, Folder 26)
    - Little Italy Days (Bloomfield), 2012-2013 (Box 63, Folder 27)
    - LJS Publishing, Inc., "Talk Magazine", 2005-2006 (Box 63, Folder 28)
    - Low Income Home Energy Assistance Program (LIHEAP), 2005-2008 (Box 63, Folder 29)
    - Lupus, 2005 (Box 63, Folder 30)
    - Magee Women's Hospital, 2003 (Box 63, Folder 31)
    - Mainstreet URA, 2000-2006 (Box 63, Folder 32)
    - Mandatory Sentencing, 2003 (Box 63, Folder 33)
    - Meadow and McDonald Street Automotive Training Center Phase II, 2009 (Box 63, Folder 34)
    - Medicare Part D, 2005 (Box 63, Folder 35)
    - Mercy Hospital, 2012 (Box 63, Folder 36)
    - Millenium Travel, 2005 (Box 63, Folder 37)
    - Mills Corp, 2003-2004 (Box 63, Folder 38)
    - Millvale, 2010 (Box 63, Folder 39)
    - Mon/Fayette Expressway and Southern Beltway Projects, 2008 (Box 63, Folder 40)